Finding Aid for the Ho Young Ham Papers LSC.0697
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 3: Books, 1873-1994; 29 boxes.
  - Subseries 3D: Miscellaneous, 1905-1934
    - Various new and old songs., ca. 1925.; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      Some text in Chinese. Color cover illustration. Author: Yi-yong Kang. Publisher: Yongch'ang Sogwan, Seoul.
  - Subseries 3E: Theology, ca. 1873-1946
    - Reconciliation in Korean., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Author: J.F. Rutherford. Publisher: Watch Tower, Bible and Tract Society. Brooklyn, New York.
    - [Bible--New Testament]., undated.; 1 item. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - [New Testament with Hymnal (Korean)]., undated.; Pocket versions. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - New Testament [Chinese], ca. 1910.; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Korean text.
    - Bible, Old Testament., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      Publisher: American Bible Society, Seoul, Korea. Printed in Japan, issued in Seoul.
    - Chan Song Ka: the hymnal of the Federal Council of Protestant Evangelical Missions in Korea., 1918.; 1 item. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      Text in English and Korean. Printed Seoul, Korea.
    - Ch'ansongga = Hymnal., 1933.; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Publishing data in Chinese. Main text is Korean and English. Publisher: Choson Yaso Kyosohoe, Seoul. Author: Ap'yon Sora. Inscription in pencil: M.E. Korean Church Camp I.
    - Ch'ansongga = Hymnal., 1925.; 2 items. (Box 18, Folder 2)
      Chinese, Korean, and English text. Author: P'iduk Moksa. Publisher: Choson Yaso Kyosohoe, Seoul = Korean Christian Book Society (or Association).
    - Ch'ansongga, 14th ed. = Hymnals [1 of 2]., 1923.; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Song titles are in English; cover sheet and text are Korean. Publisher: Choson Yaso Kyosohoe, Seoul. Copies are inscribed, respectively, Simon Ham, John Hohm, and Mary [?].
    - Ch'ansongga, 14th ed. = Hymnals [2 of 2]., 1923.; 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Song titles are in English; cover sheet and text are Korean. Publisher: Choson Yaso Kyosohoe, Seoul.
    - Chondo Chi Chogsin = Spirit of preaching the truth., 1923.; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Book title in Chinese. Korean and Chinese used in main text. Publisher: Ch'ongjin Sogwan, Seoul. Publisher: Hwalmunsa Sojom, Seoul. Original author was Japanese. Book translated from Japanese by T'ae-yong Ch'oe.
    - Chongo Soonggyohoe Kongdomun = Many kinds of prayer., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      Chinese on cover and publication data. Main text is Korean. Publisher: Taeyongguk Chong Kosong Kyohoe, Seoul.
    - Chu' ui malssum = Lord's message New Testament., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 18, Folder 7)
      Chinese used for publishing data. Korean text. Publisher: Tongyang Sowon, Seoul. Publisher: Seoul Oriental Publishing Company. Publisher: Eastern College. Author: Chun-ho Min
    - Commentary on Luke's gospel., undated.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Common people's gospel, 1st ed., 1910 December.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Preface and table of contents in English. Text in Korean. Cover missing.
    - Conference commentary on acts of the apostles, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      Translator: C.H. Min. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on epistle of James, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Conference commentary on I and II Corinthians, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Translator: Namsukee Baik. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul. OCLC locates one copy only, at Harvard.
    - Conference commentary on I and II Thessalonians, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Translator: Namsukee Baik. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on I, II and III John, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Translator: Mr. C.H. Min. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on Jude, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Conference commentary on Luke and John vol. II., ca. 1910.; 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Conference commentary on Philemon, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Translator: G.H. Min. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on Philippians, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 2)
      Translator: Sin Suk Koo. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on St. Mark's gospel, translated from the Chinese., 1911.; 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Translator: Yi Won Keung. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on St. Matthew's gospel, translated from the Chinese., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Conference commentary on the book of revelation, translated from the Chinese., 1913.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Conference commentary on the epistle to the Colossians, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 6)
      Translator: C.H. Min. By: Rev. Drs. W. Muirhead, H.C. Duboise, and C.J. Voscamp. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on the epistle to the Ephesians, translated from the Chinese., 1913.; 3 items. (Box 20, Folder 7)
      Translator: C.H. Min. By: Rev. Drs. W. Muirhead, H.C. Dubose, and C.J. Voscamp. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on the epistle to the Hebrews, translated from the Chinese., 1913.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Conference commentary on the epistle to the Romans., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Conference commentary on the gospel of Saint John., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 10)
      By: C.H. Min. Publisher: The Dong-Yang-Suh-Won. Seoul.
    - Conference commentary on the New Testament vol. II Luke and John., undated.; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 1)
      By: Rev. Drs. A.P. Parker, H.C. DuBose, and W. Muirhead. Publisher: The Religious Tract Society for China. Hankow and Shanhai.
    - Conference commentary on the New Testament vol. III, acts, epistle to the Romans, I. Corinthians, II. Corinthians, Galatians and Ephesians., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 2)
      By: Rev. Drs. W. Muirhead, H.C. DuBose, and C.J. Voskamp. Publisher: The Chinese Tract Society. Shanghai.
    - Conference commentary on the New Testament vol. III, I Corinthians, II Corinthians, Galatians and Ephesians., undated.; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 3)
      By: Drs. W. Muirhead, H.C. DuBose, and C.J. Voskamp. Publisher: The Religious Tract Society for China. Hankow and Shanghai.
    - Conference commentary on the New Testament, vol. I Mathew and Mark., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Authors: Rev Drs A.P. Parker, John Ross, and H.V. Noyes. Published by: Chinese Tract Society, Shanghai.
    - Conference commentary on the New Testament, vol. I, Mathew and Mark., ca. 1911.; 1 item. (Box 21, Folder 5)
      Authors: Drs. A.P. Parker, John Ross, and H.V. Noyes. Publisher: The Religious Tract Society for China, Hankow and Shanghai.
    - Conference commentary on the New Testament, vol. IV., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Publisher: The Religious Tract Society for China, Hankow and Shanghai. Korean text. Korean/Chinese text on binders. Double-page Asian-style. 204 pages. No illustrations. Has name C.H. Mar on inside cover. Also signature of Ham Ho Young in Chinese (in red pencil).
    - Conference Commentary on the New Testament, vol. IV, Philippians, Colossians I and II, Thessalonians I and II, Timothy, Titus, Philemon, Hebrews, James I and II, Peter I, II, III, John, Jude, and Revelation, 6th ed., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Publisher: Chinese Tract Society.
    - Conference commentary on Timothy, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Conference commentary on Titus, translated from the Chinese., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Exodus in Korean., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Publisher: American Bible Society
    - First graduates of Union Methodist Seminary., undated.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Published in Seoul, Korea. Fragile; covers missing and some pages detached.
    - Genesis., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Text is Korean. Publisher: American Bible Society. Missing cover and pages 1, 2, and 151.
    - God, His existence, attributes and nature., 1917.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 8)
      Main text is Korean. Publication data is Chinese. Publisher: Jen-Li Church, Shi_chun Theological School, Seoul. Translator and publisher: To, Yun-myong (American doctor of Theology)
    - Guide to heaven., undated.; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 9)
      Author: Ludan. Translator Na-she-ni.
    - Han'guk kyhooe p'ipak = Hardship of the church in Korean., 1913.; 2 items. (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Cover page and publishing information in Chinese. Main text is Korean. Author: Dr. Syngman Rhee = Sung-man Yi. Publisher: New Korean Newspaper, Hawaii.
    - Harmony of the gospels with outline of the life of Christ., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Korean text. Author: John H. Kerr, D.D. Publisher: American Tract Society
    - Helps to Bible study., 1909.; 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Title page in English. Publisher: S.D.A. Mission Press. Seoul, Korea.
    - Holy Bible, Old Testament., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Korean text. Published by British and Foreign Bible Society
    - I Samuel in Korean., 1908.; 2 items. (Box 24, Folder 1)
      Publisher: American Bible Society.
    - Isaiah in Korean., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      Publisher: British and Foreign Bible Society.
    - Isle Jingo to sampan annoy = I-Se shrine and worship information., 1925.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 3)
      Illustrations include maps and photos. Editor: Kawasaki Seigo. Published: Tokyo.
    - Kangdo Ch'wijip = Comprehensive understanding of the Bible., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      Cover and publication data in Chinese; main text in Korean. Publisher: Pogup Sogwan, Seoul = Pogup Bookstore. Author: American Missionary Andrew, translated by Sun Hyon.
    - Kidohoe Chemok = One day at a time, a month of prayers., 1899.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Text is Korean. Publisher: Kurisudo Sinmun'guk = Christ Publishing Company, Seoul, Korea.
    - Kidokkyo ui chinsu = Who is God?., 1935.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 6)
      Text in Chinese and Korean. Author: Myong-jik Yi, P.E. Haines (Missionary). Publisher: Tongyang Son'gyohoe Songgyol Kyohoe = Oriental Mission Society for America Publisher, Seoul.
    - Kongsumun = Four kinds of prayer., undated.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Title page in Chinese. Main text in Chinese and Korean. Publisher: Taeyongguk Chong Kosong Kyohoe, Seoul. Publisher: Korean Bible Society Episcopal Church, Seoul.
    - Korean New Testament in mixed script., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Publisher: British & Foreign Bible Society, Seoul, Korea.
    - Korean New Testament in mixed script., 1935.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Kuse non = Savior (story of human being, god saved all)., undated.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Kyonghomsang uro odun na ui chongygogwan = My view of religion., 1936.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 11)
      Chinese and Korean text. Author: Ch'ang-song Yi. Publisher: Hansong Toso Chusik Hoesa, Seoul = Seoul Bookstore Association, Seoul. Picture of author [?]
    - Life of John Wesley., 1916.; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 12)
      Author: Reverend Nehemiah Curnock. Translated by: Rev. J. Robert Moose. Publisher: Korean Religious Tract Society. Chong-no, Seoul.
    - Mansa Songch'wi = How to be a good Christian., 1916.; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Korean and Chinese text. Publisher: Kwangmyong Sogwan, P'yongyang. Author: Son-ju Kil
    - New covenant commonly called The New Testament of our Lord and savior Jesus Christ., 1901.; 4.75" X 3.5". (Box 25, Folder 2)
      English text. Publisher: Thomas Nelson & Sons.
    - New Testament., ca. 1946.; 3 items. (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Pocket versions. Various publishers. One copy inscribed "Miss Salome Ham"; one copy inscribed to Juliette Ow from "Auntie Clara."
    - New Testament., ca. 1910.; 2 items. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - New Testament in Chinese., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Published in China.
    - New Testament in Korean., undated.; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Publishing information: "Printed by the Bible Committee of Korea, the British and Foreign Bible Society, the American Bible Society, and the National Bible Society of Scotland by the Methodist Publishing House, Tokyo, Japan." Inscription in pencil: "Compliment of Mr. Ham Ho Yong. Bought in the year of 1921."
    - New Testament references., 1935.; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Title page in English. Color illustrations. Publisher: British & Foreign Bible Society. Seoul, Korea.
    - Nut'o kaegyo kaeryak = Book of Martin Luther theory., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      Author: Reverend James S. Gale, D.D. Publisher: Kwanghak Sop'o, Seoul. Text is Korean.
    - Old Testament history, 2nd ed., 1913.; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      Title page in English. Korean text. Prepared by: Rev. W.L. Swallen. Publisher: the Presbyterian Publication Fund. The Korean Religious Tract Society. Seoul, Korea.
    - Old Testament in Korean., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 26, Folder 5)
      Title page in English; main text is Korean. Publisher: American Bible Society. "Ham Ho Yong" inscribed in pencil on front cover. "Ham Ho Young" inscribed in pen on back cover.
    - Old Testament in Korean., 1911.; 2 items. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Old Testament second book., 1911.; 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 2)
      Korean text. Publisher: American Bible Society, Seoul, Korea.
    - Old Testament: Samuel I and II., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Cover text in Korean and Chinese. Text is in Korean. Publication data in Chinese. Publisher: Tongyang Sowon, Seoul. Fragile condition.
    - Outline studies on the life of Jesus (from the Cleveland Y.M.C.A.)., 1913.; 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Korean and English text. Adapted and translated by F.M. Brockman and Reigh Won Chang. Publisher: The Korean Religious Tract Society. Seoul, Korea.
    - Paikmok Kangyun = Sermons by One Hundred Pastors & Teachers, vol. 1., 1921.; 1 item. (Box 27, Folder 5)
      English and Chinese used in title page and publishing data. Main text in is Korean. Publisher: Pangmun Sogwan, Seoul = Pangmun Bookstore, Seoul. Stamp on back page "Rev. C.H. Mar, PO Box 43, Paia Maui Hawaii."
    - Paikmok Kangyun = Sermons by one hundred pastors & teachers, vol. 2., 1922.; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 1)
      English and Chinese used in title page and publishing data. Main text in is Korean. Publisher: Pangmun Sogwan, Seoul = Pangmun Bookstore, Seoul.
    - Paikmok Kangyun = Sermons by one hundred pastors & teachers, vol. 3., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Psalms in Korean., 1908.; 2 items. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Psalms in Korean., 1906.; 2 items. (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Printed for the Bible Committee of Korea, by the Fukuin Printing Co., Yokohama, Japan.
    - Psalms in Korean., 1909.; 2 items. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Rightly dividing the word of God, section I of Dr. C.I. Schofield's Bible course., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Korean and English text. Translated by Rev. W.L. Swallen. Presbyterian Publication Fund.
    - Samuel I., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Samuel II and Kings I and II., 1908.; 1 item. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      Main text is Korean, with three sections in English. Front and back cover missing. Publisher: American Bible Society.
    - Sheffield's universal history, translated from the Chinese by students of the Pyeng Yang Union College and Academy, volume I, II and IV., ca. 1911.; 4 items. (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Translated under the direction of Rev. W.M. Baird, PhD and Annie L.A. Baird. Includes maps.
    - Sinang ui ro = Sermons by Rev. Kim Jk Too., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 29, Folder 2)
      Title page and publishing data in English and Chinese. Main text Chinese and Korean. Publisher: Pangmun Sogak, Seoul. Author: Ik-jong No.
    - Sinyak Choson = The Korean New Testament, mixed script., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 29, Folder 3)
      Chinese and Korean text. Inscription: "Property of Ham Ho Young." Publisher: Pogum Inswae Hapcha Hoesa.
    - Sinyak choso Ch'ansongga happu = Bible, New Testament and hymnal., 1914.; 1 item. (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Title page and publication data in Chinese. Main text is Korean. Publisher: Choson Yaso Kyosohoe, Seoul. Publisher: Korean Christian Book Society. Author: Wanggil Moksa.
    - Sinyak Choson = New Testament., 1911.; 2 items. (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Title page in Chinese. Main text is Korean. Author: Sung-gon Han. Publisher: Choson Yesugyo Changnohoe, P'yongyang, Korea = Jesuit Presbyterian Association, P'yongyang, Korea.
    - Sinyak Syonggyong Kwa ansigil = Part of Old Testament, work six days and one days rest., 1915.; 1 item. (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Author: Chong Chae-Sun. Publisher: Kyongsong Tongdae Munoe Pyongjom-ni, Seoul = East Gate Outside Cookie Store, neighborhood community.
    - Sip'yon Ch'alyo = Psalms, Old Testament., 1898.; 1 item. (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Text Korean. Published: Seoul. Author: P'it'osu (Pieters, A. A.)
    - Songgyo idung = Witness of Holy Spirit., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Cover and publishing information in Chinese. Main text is Korean. Publisher: Tae Yongguk kosong Kyohoe = British Publishing Church.
    - Songhoe Kongga = Hymn of Holy Spirit., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Cover text and publishing data in Chinese. Main text is Korean. Publisher: Taehan Songgonghoe [Great Korea Holy Union Publisher]. Red cloth cover. Ham family names are written in pencil on last page of book. Pages are deteriorating.
    - Studies in the life of Christ, 2nd ed., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Title page in English. Includes illustrations and map of Israel. Author: Rev. W.L. Swallen. Publisher: Presbyterian Publication Fund. The Korean Religious Tract Society. Seoul, Korea.
    - Su Pogum taeji puhap = Four gospels of the New Testament: Mark, Luke, John, and Matthew., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Korean text. Publisher: P'yongyang Yesugyo Sowon and Kyongsong Yesugyo Sohoe. Publisher: Seoul and Pyong Yang Organization Missionary.
    - Sunday school lessons, senior course., 1921.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Prepared by B.W. Billings and Peninsula S. Hahn. Published for The Federal Council of Protestant Missions in Korea by the Christian Literature Society of Korea. Dust cover made from Chinese newspaper.
    - Sunday school lessons, teacher's handbook., 1921.; 2 items. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      Title page in English. Published for The Federal Council of Protestant Missions in Korea. Prepared by: B.W. Billings and Peninsula S. Han. Christian Literature Society of Korea.
    - Sun'gyoja = Little book., 1933.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Cover and title page are in Chinese. Main text is Korean. Author: Yong-t'aek Chon. Publisher: Hansong Toso Chusik Hoesa, Seoul = Seoul Bookstore Association.
    - Syere mundap = Questions and answers on baptism., 1906.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Entire text in Korean. Publisher: Methodist Publishing House, Seoul. Fragile condition.
    - Syongsyo Kangmok = Index for Bible keywords., undated.; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - The doctrines of discipline of the Methodist Episcopal Church., 1910.; 2 items. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      Translated by E.M.Cable and Cho Myung-ha.
    - The essentials of Christianity., 1916.; 1 item. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Author: Henry C. Sheldon, D.D. Translated by Cho Sang Ok and Choi Chi Wan under the direction of C.S. Deming, S.T.D.
    - The great controversy: the conflict of the ages in the Christian dispensation, volume II., 1938.; 2 items. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Author: Ellen G. White. Publisher: Signs of the Times Publishing House. Seoul (Seiryori Machi) Chosen.
    - The human heart, 3rd ed., 1914.; 1 item. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      Title page in English. Translated by Rev. W.M. Baird, D.D. Publisher: the Korean Religious Tract Society. Seoul, Korea.
    - Treatise on the book of Daniel., 1912.; 1 item. (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Author: Mimi Scharffenberg. Publisher: The Korean S.D.A. Mission Press, Seoul, Korea.
    - Why I believe in religion., ca. 1935.; 1 item. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Author: Charles R. Brown.
    - Yiyu yogi; Hawaii Hanin Kyobsa = Explanation of terms of the Bible., 1910.; 1 item. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Korean text. Cover art of beach scene. Publisher: Hawaii Hanin Kyobosya, Honolulu. Publisher: Hawaii, Korean Publishing Company.
    - Yonghae mundap = Questions/answers., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Cover text and publication data in Chinese. Main text is Korean. Publisher: Taeyongguk Chonggo Songgyohoe, Seoul. Publisher: British Missionary Episcopal, Seoul, Korea. Subject: Christian philosophy.
    - Holy Bible containing the Old and New Testaments, translated out of the original tongues...[salesman's sample?]., 1873.; 1 item. (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Publisher: James Betts & Co., Hartford, Conn., Chicago, Ills. Includes illustrations by Gustave Doré and engravings by J.R. Rice and John C. McRae. Does not appear to be a full-text bible.
  - Subseries 3F: Yearbooks, 1932-1950
    - Green and White, Molokai High School., 1950.; 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Korean Students' Annual--Korean Student Alliance 1932., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Publisher: The Korean Students' Alliance of Hawaii under the auspices of the Korean Student Christian Movement of Hawaii.
    - Korean Students' Annual--Korean Student Alliance 1933., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      Volume II, McKinley number. Cover inscribed with Elizabeth Hahm's name. Publisher: The Korean Students' Alliance of Hawaii under the auspices of the Korean Student Christian Movement of Hawaii.
    - Korean Students' Annual--Korean Student Alliance 1935-1936., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Volume V, University number. Publisher: The Korean Students' Alliance of Hawaii under the auspices of the Korean Student Christian Movement of Hawaii.
    - Korean Students' Annual--Korean Student Alliance 1936-1937., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      Volume VI, Korean number. Publisher: The Korean Students' Alliance of Hawaii under the auspices of the Korean Student Christian Movement of Hawaii.
    - Korean Students' Annual--Korean Student Alliance 1937-1938., 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      Volume VII, Scenic Hawaii. Publisher: the Korean Students of Hawaii under the auspices of The Korean Students' Christian Movement of Hawaii.
    - Korean Students' Annual--Korean Students of Hawaii Yearbook 1939-40., 1940.; 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      Volume IX, second University number. Publisher: The Korean Students of Hawaii under the auspices of Korean Students' Christian Movement.
    - Silversword, Volume 19, Maui High School., 1937.; 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Inscribed "Dora Ham."
    - Silversword, Volume 20, Maui High School., 1938.; 2 items. (Box 32, Folder 9)
      One copy inscribed "Dora Ham" and includes notations and signatures from friends.
    - Silversword, Volume 21, Maui High School., 1939.; 2 items. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      One copy inscribed "Elizabeth Ham," the other inscribed "John Ham."
    - Silversword, Volume 23, Maui High School., 1941.; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Embossed on cover "Paul Ham." Includes notations and signatures from friends.
    - Silversword, Volume 24, Maui High School., 1942.; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Silversword, Volume 25, Maui High School., 1943.; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Silversword, Volume 28, Maui High School., 1946.; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 5)